[Music]
[âm nhạc]
If there are weary notes
Nếu có những nốt mỏi mệt
from deep within the heart wanting to find peace, If you
từ tận trong tâm muốn tìm yên bình Nếu
want to illuminate your soul, then
muốn soi sáng tâm hồn
leave the bustling city for a while, pack your bags, my friend, let's
thì tạm xa nơi thành phố xô bồ xách ba
meet in a moment,
ta gặp nhau phút
from all directions, towards simplicity.
từ khắp muôn phương hướng về đơn
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
Our hearts are as bright as the moon in the
giản đôi tâm ta trăng sáng giữa đêm
waning night, a place that gives us everything.
trăng tàn nơi cho ta tất cả với
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
Together we connect, love is so strong, my friend, this
cùng nhau kết nối yêu thương quá tôi mùa
summer, let's sing together, a connection of friendship from all
hè năm cùng nhau hay hát vang
directions. [
một kết nối muôn Phương tình bạn
Music] I
[âm nhạc]
still remember, just yesterday we were
vẫn nhớ Vừa mới hôm nào
shy, only saying hello, but
ngại ngùng bên nhau chỉ nói câu chào đêm
tonight so much has happened,
nay thì đã bao điều
sitting together, sharing our feelings,
cùng ngồi bên nhau sẻ chia tâm tình
pack your bags, my friend, let's
dại ba lô lên bạn ơi
meet through this summer, a connection of
ta gặp nhau qua tu mùa hè
friendship from all directions. [Music] I still remember, just yesterday we were shy together, only saying hello, but tonight we have so much to share, sitting together, sharing our innocent hearts, pack your bags, my friend, let's meet through this summer, a connection of friendship from all directions,
khắc muôn Phương
where I am going, a place I really like, just needing to be pure
nơi tôi đang rất thích chỉ cần
in the waning night, a place that
ta trong sáng giữa đêm trăng tàn nơi cho
connects us with so many friends, I
ta gắn kết với bao bạn bè
don't want to leave. Come on, let's come here
không muốn về Nào Cùng nhau hãy đến đây
together, let's connect, love is so sad, this
cùng nhau kết nối yêu thương thật buồn
summer we fly and sing together,
Mùa Hè nào cùng nhau bay hát vang
love.
Yêu Thương
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
Happy together, for so long, still remembering, forgetting
vui bên nhau lúc lâu ngày vẫn còn Quên
sorrow like the moment we are together, angels happy when
sầu như phút bên nhau thiên thần vui khi
not connected, from all directions. Oh, my heart is filled with longing,
không kết nối Muôn Mặt về Ôi tim ta lưu
happy, I don't want to leave.
luyến vui không muốn về
[Music]
[âm nhạc]